# Vrushit Patel

## Associate Consultant at VMware

Always been eager to learn and develop more skills. I have been coding for the last 7 years and am proficient in C++, JavaScript and Python. Have also attained good practice in Web Development as a Full Stack. Visit my website here: <a href="mailto:vrushitpatel.github.io">vrushitpatel.github.io</a>

#### vrushit7506@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/vrushit-patel

7506025868

github.com/vrushitpatel

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Associate Consultant**

**VMware** 

07/2022 - Present

Mumbai, India

Working with the Cloud Automation Team, and learning VMware's Stack to help out our clients.

# Web Developer

Maw & Paw

03/2022 - 06/2022

Mumbai, India

Achievements/Tasks

 Developed and maintain their E-commerce website, serving Dog and Cats Products. I help them to update any content or resolve any runtime error. Help them with any other technical support.

# Web Developer (Remote Job)

Aepiphanni Business Consulting

06/2021 - 02/2022

Atlanta, Georgia

Task

 Developed Websites for their clients, each having different functionalities. Creating User-friendly, Responsive and Visually Impressive Websites.

# OpenCV Software Intern

Software Workshop Technologies Pvt. Ltd

04/2021 - 06/2021

Task

 Build a software using OpenCV in Python for tracking activities of multiple people in a single room. It also generates the report by assigning each person a unique ID.

## **EDUCATION**

# B.Tech. Computer Science

NMIMS MPSTME

06/2018 - 04/2022

CGPA - 3.78 / 4.00

# **12th ISC** SVKM CNM School

06/2016 - 04/2018

Batch Topper: 90.50%

## **SKILLS**



# PERSONAL PROJECTS

Bar Stock Exchange Dine-in Ordering (03/2021 - 04/2021)

 Bar Stock Exchange is a dine-in ordering software implementing a stock market theme, build using **Django**. This software implements **Dynamic** and **Asynchronous** features using **JavaScript**, **AJAX**, **JSON** and **NLTK**.

# Implement Level 2 Of Self Driving In GTA V (08/2020 - 09/2020)

 Implement Self Driving Car (Level 2) using Image Processing (Python) in which it detects nearby objects and lane detection in a game called GTA V. It informs the driver to stop or if any signboard is nearby.

# Med-Bay Website (09/2020 - 10/2020) 🗹

Made a website for searching doctors and hospitals nearby.
Implemented HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX and PHP. Full
Dynamic Website with login and posting blogs features. View Website.

#### Made Multiple Websites For Business

 Helped many businesses by making their shops go online in this pandemic. Here are some of the companies and their website with whom I collaborated: <u>RDA System</u>, <u>Kina Arnold</u>, <u>Maw&Paw</u>, <u>Activated</u> and many more.

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### Hack-N-Code 4.0 Hackathon

Was First Runner Up in this Hackathon. The website is using the News API and Infographics to show how climate changes.

## **CORE COMPETENCY**

Problem Solving	Critical Thinking	Leadership	
Communication	Smart Working	Teamwork	